https://www.bcuplastics.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode

BCU Plastics
Search:
800-753-5178Call us to place an order
Home
Bags & Packaging Supplies
Commercial Vacuum Bags & TubingPolypropylene BagsPre-opened bagsTextured "Channel" Vacuum Bags and RollsStand Up PouchesClear Stand Up PouchesFoil Stand Up PouchesMatte Stand Up PouchesMylar Stand Up PouchesOval Window Stand Up PouchesRice Paper Stand Up PouchesFoil with Valve Stand Up PouchesMatte with Valve Stand Up PouchesOval Window with Valve Stand Up PouchesMylar with Valve Stand Up PouchesTrash LinersLinear Low DensityHeavyweight LinersHigh DensityDrum LinersPoly BagsFlat Packed in CasesFlat on RollsGusseted Packed in CasesGusseted on RollsBag Closing TiesShrinkPOF Shrink Film Center FoldPVC Shrink Film Center FoldShrink BagsSpecialty BagsBag Closing TiesPoly Tubing and Dispenser RacksStatic Control BagsReclosable Zipper BagsPallet Covers and Bin LinersBin and Gaylord Liners Pallet Size Shrink Bags on RollsPallet Top Covers - BLACK with UVI/UVAPallet Top SheetingPerforated Clear Sheeting on RollsBopp Resealable Lip-N-TapePostal Mailing Bags
Sealers & Equipment
Commercial Vacuum SealersAmerivacs SealersAmerivacs Parts and AccesoriesHIPPO Vacuum SealerSeco-Gramatech SealersWeston Chamber Sealer and BagsTable Top ChambersSingle ChambersDouble ChambersDouble Impulse SealersCulinary and Sous VideThermal CirculatorsSous Vide SuppliesVacuum SealersWeston Vacuum Sealers and PartsDirect Heat SealersShrink SystemsShrink Wrap SystemsShrink Wrap SealersHeat GunsBand SealersHand SealersHand Impulse SealerHand Impulse Sealer with CutterI Bar SealersL-Bar SealersPortable Hand SealersHand Sealer PartsCarton SealersFoot SealersFoot Impulse SealersDouble Impulse Foot SealersDirect Heat Foot SealersReplacement KitsParts - TISF 302 & 305Parts - TISF 452 & 455Parts - TISF 602 & 605Parts - FS 358F, 458F & 658FParts for TISF Foot SealersParts for FS Foot SealersParts for THS Foot SealersAir Pillow EquipmentAutomatic SealersPallet Wrappers - Turn TablesHigh Profile WrappersLow Profile Wrappers
Menu
Home
Bags & Packaging Supplies
Commercial Vacuum Bags & TubingTextured "Channel" Vacuum Bags and RollsPoly Bags Flat Packed in CasesFlat on RollsGusseted Packed in CasesGusseted on RollsBag Closing TiesPoly Tubing and Dispenser RacksReclosable Zipper BagsBopp Resealable Lip-N-TapePolypropylene BagsStand Up Pouches Clear Stand Up PouchesFoil Stand Up PouchesMatte Stand Up PouchesMylar Stand Up PouchesOval Window Stand Up PouchesRice Paper Stand Up PouchesFoil with Valve Stand Up PouchesMatte with Valve Stand Up PouchesOval Window with Valve Stand Up PouchesMylar with Valve Stand Up PouchesShrink POF Shrink Film Center FoldPVC Shrink Film Center FoldShrink BagsStatic Control BagsPallet Covers and Bin Liners Bin and Gaylord Liners Pallet Size Shrink Bags on RollsPallet Top Covers - BLACK with UVI/UVAPallet Top SheetingPerforated Clear Sheeting on RollsPostal Mailing BagsPre-opened bagsTrash Liners Linear Low DensityHeavyweight LinersHigh DensityDrum LinersSpecialty Bags Bag Closing Ties
Sealers & Equipment
Commercial Vacuum Sealers Amerivacs SealersAmerivacs Parts and AccesoriesHIPPO Vacuum SealerSeco-Gramatech SealersWeston Chamber Sealer and BagsTable Top ChambersSingle ChambersDouble ChambersWeston Vacuum Sealers and PartsShrink Systems Shrink Wrap SystemsShrink Wrap SealersHeat GunsHand Sealers Hand Impulse SealerHand Impulse Sealer with CutterI Bar SealersL-Bar SealersPortable Hand SealersHand Sealer PartsFoot Sealers Foot Impulse SealersDouble Impulse Foot SealersDirect Heat Foot SealersReplacement KitsParts - TISF 302 & 305Parts - TISF 452 & 455Parts - TISF 602 & 605Parts - FS 358F, 458F & 658FParts for TISF Foot SealersParts for FS Foot SealersParts for THS Foot SealersAutomatic SealersDouble Impulse SealersDirect Heat SealersBand SealersCarton SealersAir Pillow EquipmentPallet Wrappers - Turn Tables High Profile WrappersLow Profile WrappersCulinary and Sous Vide Thermal CirculatorsSous Vide SuppliesVacuum Sealers
0
$0.00
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Please replace this text with you Privacy Policy.
Please add any additional cookies your website uses below (e.g., Google Analytics)
This privacy policy sets out how BCU Plastics & Packaging Supplies uses and protects any information
that you give BCU Plastics & Packaging Supplies when you use this website.
BCU Plastics & Packaging Supplies is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.
Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website,
then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
BCU Plastics & Packaging Supplies may change this policy from time to time by updating this page.
You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service,
and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we
think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.
We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website
according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure,
we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure
the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive.
Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit
a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application
can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about
your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic
and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical
analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful
and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you,
other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting
to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links
to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website.
Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst
visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.
You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate
that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes,
you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at
sales@bcuplastics.com
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission
or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information
about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998.
A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to
30724 Benton Road, Suite C302 #560, Winchester,
CA 92596.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete,
please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address.
We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE name
COOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
Superior Service
Friendly and Knowledgeable Staff
quick shipping
We get your orders to you fast.
competitive pricing
The best prices in the business.
Experienced Staff
Our staff knows the products inside and out.
QUALITY PRODUCTS
Extensive quality control so you get the best.
About Us
At BCU our goal is to fulfill your packaging needs. Whether you are an electronics firm in a clean room environment, a restaurant or food supplier who needs FDA approved bags,or anyone with a reason to seal or package something...We can help!
Please browse and shop on our website, or call us at 800-753-5178.
Customer Service
My account
Shipping & Returns
About Us
Contact Us
Advanced Product Search
What Our Customers Say
"Your service is the best. Thank you.
-Joe
WA
"Thanks so much for your quick service.
-Alex
CA
"It is a joy to order from you. Very fast from coast to coast.
-KB
NC
"I just wanted to let you know that I received the bags with plenty of time to get ready for our event. I want to thank you for the expeditious manner with which you handled my order.
-
TX
"Thanks for great customer service. Your company and staff are second to none. Expect another order shortly. I am now a loyal BCU Plastics customer and highly recommend your products.
-
TX
"A company way above the ordinary. Thanks.
-
WA
"Thank you very much your service was exceptional. You went above and beyond. Thank you.
Help Us to Keep Magento Healthy - Report All Bugs (ver. 1.9.0.1)
© 2015 BCU Plastics. All right reserved.
Terms of Use -
Privacy Policy -
Site Map
Website developed by
